<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cascadia Systems Institute</title>
    <link>https://cascadia-systems.institute/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cascadia Systems Institute</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 20:31:48 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cascadia-systems.institute/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://cascadia-systems.institute/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 20:31:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cascadia-systems.institute/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Please send us an email contact@cascadia-systems.institute</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting</title>
      <link>https://cascadia-systems.institute/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 18:45:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cascadia-systems.institute/consulting/</guid>
      <description> Consulting Services  Whole Systems Benchmarking Resilience Assessments Complex Data Analysis Investigation of Complex, Systemic, or &amp;ldquo;Wicked&amp;rdquo; Problems Multi-Stakeholder Problem Solving Facilitation Transdiciplinary Problem Solving Systemic Intervention Design  Toolkit  Soft Systems Facilitation Techniques Causal Loop Diagramming Resilience Assessments Systems Dynamics Modeling Agent Based Modeling Network Analysis Data Mining/Modeling Machine Learning  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://cascadia-systems.institute/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 17:51:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cascadia-systems.institute/about/</guid>
      <description>Cascadia Systems Institute The Cascadia Systems Institute is an academic research organization which seeks to make practical improvements to the systems which make up our current civilization.
The 21st century is a time of great change and accelerating complexity in social, political, economic, technological, and ecological/climatic systems. These systems are coupled in such a way that changes in any one system or subsystem may result in changes, good or bad, to any or all of the connected systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://cascadia-systems.institute/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 17:51:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cascadia-systems.institute/team/</guid>
      <description>The CSI Team   Roderick Campbell Education  PhD Candidate, Organizational Systems (Saybrook University) M.S. Public Policy and Management (Carnegie Mellon University) B.S. Social Science/Economics (University of California, Berkeley)  Professional Experience  Chair, Student Special Integration Group at the International Societyfor the Systems Sciences (ISSS) Council Member at Gerson Lehrman Group Organizational Services Consultant at Forest &amp;amp; Einstein, Inc. Associate Governmental Program Analyst at the California Department of Education Advisor for Policy and Planning at California Electricity Oversight Board Senior Consultant atCalifornia State Assembly &amp;amp; Senate Public Utilities Regulatory Analyst at California Public Utilities Commission  Research Interests  Applied Systems Practice Public Policy &amp;amp; Administration Complex Problem Solving    Peter Roolf Education  PhD Student, Systems Science (Portland State University) M.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>